# BARTOSZ STANIECKO

SYSTEMS MANAGEMENT SPECIALIST

#### CONTACT

+48 513 666 213



pearlzfan@pm.me



www.linkedin.com/in/bartstan



Al. Niepodleglosci 16/30 43-100 Tychy

## **FEATURES**

Logical thinking Open-minded Planning / Organizing Teamplayer

## TECH SKILLS

RedHat Ansible Automation Platform HCL BigFix

MS Windows Server

Powershell

Yaml

Sonatype Nexus Repository Manager GitHub

## **EDUCATION**

# University of Silesia

2015-2019

Cultural Studies - PhD

2011-2015

Cultural Studies - Master's Degree

2000-2004

Mathematics and Computer Science

# LANGUAGES

Polish

English

German

Japanese



#### BIOGRAPHY

I am a seasoned automation and systems management specialist with over a decade of experience serving international clients both remotely and on-site. Presently, I hold the role of Ansible Tower Account Administrator, tasked with automating a range of infrastructure services patching, Security Health Checks, UIDEXT, and includina hardware/software scans. My expertise lies in process management following ITIL methodology, implementing and administering automation tools for managed systems, and CI/CD pipelines. Additionally, I am wellversed in Agile practices, ensuring efficient and collaborative project execution.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

## Systems administrator - RedHat Ansible Tower

Kyndryl Global Services Delivery Center Polska

Oct 2021 - present

- RedHat Ansible Automation Platform account administration (4 orgs, approximately 11000 hosts).
- Troubleshooting playbook problems and issues (Windows/Unix platforms).
- Maintaining security health check process automation.
- Playbooks development to automate routine tasks and events.
- Managing Sonatype Nexus Repository Manager 3.
- Managing Tower account organizations, inventories, users, credentials.
- Preparing manuals, tutorials and trainings for new employees.
- Completed migration of HWSW Currency Management System, SFIT, UIDEXT and Security Health Checks from BigFix to Ansible.

## Systems administrator - HCL BigFix

IBM Client Innovation Center

Apr 2017 - Mar 2021

- BigFix maintenance including main server (4 instances), console, relays, client installations (approx 13000 hosts), upgrades and configuration.
- Troubleshooting IBM BigFix problems and issues (Windows/Unix platforms).
- BigFix Compliance server administration.
- Maintaining security health check process and customization.

During my time as BigFix administrator I took part in:

- Translating of ITCM scripts (ksh, sh, psl, vb) and preparing them to work in BigFix environment (project required work on client's site in Paris).
- Migrating of BigFix environment (6 relays, 6000 endpoints) under new BigFix server in new domain (work done on client's site in Luxembourg).
- Preparing BigFix infrastructure for GDPR implementation
- Migrating of BigFix infrastructure to new VLAN (1 server, 12 relays, 7000 endpoints).

# Service Desk Specialist

itWorks S.A.

Mar 2009 - Mar 2017

- User's technical support; solving issues related to office hardware and software (problems with MS Windows, MS Office; network settings configuration; hardware and software installations etc.).
- Administration of email accounts in Lotus Notes and MS Exchange.
- Administration of user's accounts in Active Directory.